Kasuga, I'm sorry.
It's something
I just can't leave unsettled.
The two of us...
...started going out yesterday.
- What?
- No way!
Seriously, Kasuga?
You gotta be kidding!
Why, Nanako?
What on earth do you see in him?
Kasuga knows so many things
people don't know about!
Kasuga, you must've used up
all the luck in your whole life!
This can't be happening!
I thought you were one of us, Kasuga!
- Right?
- Ouch!
- Stop it, guys!
- Walk home with us, just today.
- Everything's fine.
- But why? How?
I'm sure he's no fun to walk home with.
Man, it's been a long time
since my heart felt this light.
Come on, man!
- Tell us everything! Be honest!
- Cut it out.
How is it that you can get a girlfriend
and we can't?
- Were you all right yesterday?
- What?
I hope you didn't catch a cold.
Ah...
Are you all right?
You can't look!
You see... That was...
Why would anyone do
something so terrible to you?
I wonder who did it.
Uh...
I'll make an exception
and support you.
I won't expose you
as a perverted gym clothes thief, either.
I know, right?
Sorry for leaving like that.
It's okay.
Was it a bad idea
to tell everyone that we started dating?
Did you mind?
No... Not at all.
You know,
I don't know a whole lot about you yet.
I'd like to get to know you better.
So...
Let's cherish what we have
and take it slow. Okay?
Of course.
We'll cherish what we have.
I guess we're boyfriend...
and girlfriend now.
Aren't we?
Bye, then.
Boyfriend and girlfriend...
Boyfriend and girlfriend!
:cue
THE FLOWERS OF EVIL
Mega serving,
extra chunks, please.
Coming right up.
EPISODE 3
- Hey, Kasuga, let's eat together.
- Sure.
With Nakamura too.
What?
Kasuga?
Yum, this is great.
What the heck is going on here?
What is Nakamura thinking?
Saeki too. Why?
Kasuga, I didn't know
you were friends with Nakamura.
Friends?
Yeah. Nakamura told me.
- Right.
- Yeah.
Hey, Kasuga.
Is it fun dating Saeki?
Does it make you happy?
Oh, yeah.
How about you, Saeki?
Do you really like Kasuga?
Yeah.
Would you still like him
even if he were a pervert?
A pervert?
Kasuga isn't the type. Right?
Right, right.
You know what, then?
Let me tell you
what Kasuga was wearing on your date--
What? Are you okay?
Here, Kasuga, use this.
- I'll go get a towel.
- Sorry.
Why would you say that?
I thought you said you'd support me.
I did.
So, I thought I'd help
by telling her the true you--
No, you can't--
Kasuga, you're all wet. Are you all right?
Yeah, sorry.
I'll wipe this up.
- All dry?
- Yeah.
MEET ME BEHIND THE SCHOOL AFTER CLASS.
Nanako.
Hi, Ai.
If Kasuga's not coming,
let's go home together.
Thanks, but I think
I'll try waiting a little more.
- Okay, then.
- Yeah.
- Careful on your way home.
- Sure, see you.
What do you want?
Kasuga, wouldn't you like to know
how Saeki actually feels about you?
What?
The messy, grimy stuff
Saeki's hiding from you...
I could drag it all out.
I'll share everything with you, Kasuga.
Please leave us alone!
We're trying to cherish what we have
and take things slow.
I know you want to know.
If you really like her, face everything
that spills out when I crack her.
- Kasuga, you pervert!
- I am not!
I...
I'll tell you.
Saeki's true feelings...
She wants to...
have sex with you, Kasuga!
That's what she really wants.
What?
:cue
KASUGA
Kasuga, wouldn't you like to know
how Saeki actually feels about you?
Face everything that spills out
when I crack her.
SAEKI
Kasuga...
I want to have sex with...
My true self...
I need to tell Saeki...
my sins...
As if I could ever tell her!
Baudelaire,
I will overcome my past and start over!
I will become a proper person
worthy of Saeki!
That's right.
I get to see that angel tomorrow again!
Too bad your beloved Saeki has a cold.
Feeling lonely, Kasuga?
Shut up!
What was that, Kasuga?
Keep it down.
Sorry, sir.
Kasuga!
So, Kasuga,
what did you do to Nanako?
What?
She called me last night.
And she was crying.
What?
No... I mean, I didn't...
I don't know what happened,
but how dare you make Nanako cry!
Why don't you drop this off at her house?
Bye.
This is an announcement
for our citizens...
Did you come to have sex?
What?
Hey!
Hello?
Yes?
I... I brought homework!
For Saeki...
I mean, for Nanako...
I brought it for her.
I'm Kasuga, with the homework!
No need to be so formal.
Come on in.
Thank you, ma'am.
Just a moment.
I'm coming in.
Sure.
Come in.
Kasuga?
He brought over
homework for you.
Make yourself at home.
Thank you, ma'am.
Ah...
Your cold... Are you all right?
Yeah.
Ah.
You know,
I was reading this today, but...
it's pretty difficult.
I'm going to work on it
and read to the end.
Sure.
:cue
I wanted to ask you.
Kinoshita told me...
Did something happen yesterday?
Kasuga.
Come...
sit over here.
We said
we would cherish what we have, right?
What do you think
"cherish what we have" means?
The smell of her shampoo...
If you're hiding something from me,
please tell me.
If I'm hiding something?
I'm...
not a strong person.
The strong me everybody sees...
That isn't who I truly am.
Kasuga, when you sincerely
told me how you felt,
it made me really happy.
But I'm weak, so...
I'm already losing faith in it.
So, please tell me.
Tell me the truth about you.
I'm...
The truth is, I'm...
not hiding anything from you.
Really?
Yes, really.
Okay.
I believe you, Kasuga.
How's it going?
Were you able to do it?
THE FLOWERS OF EVIL
I've...
I've added to my sins, once again.
Saeki believed someone like me.
She even read The Flowers of Evil for me.
I'm scum!
I'm a shit bug!
Yes, you are.
I beg you, Nakamura!
I can't ask anyone else.
Please tell Saeki
that I stole her gym clothes.
Tell her what I truly am!
That's great.
Kasuga,
you've got a great look on your face.
Sure.
I'll help you.
:cue
What are you going to do?
Look at the moon, Kasuga.
It's as if it's bulging, about to burst.
Hurry up.
Write.
Everything about
who you really are, Kasuga.
What?
How you stole Nanako Saeki's gym clothes,
that you rubbed them all over your body,
that you wore them on your date
and confessed your love wearing it.
That you're scum, an utter pervert.
Write that it's all you, Takao Kasuga.
Then, if we leave the gym clothes here,
you can get Saeki to see it all tomorrow.
I did not rub them all over!
Besides, if I did that,
everybody would find out.
Of course they will!
Now, start writing already!
No, I don't... This isn't what I asked...
I can't believe your audacity.
You think you can just confess to Saeki
and walk away clean?
Not only that, but have me do it for you?
Stop acting so high and mighty,
and hiding your true self!
I just...
I just want to become a person
that's worthy of Saeki.
A person that's clean
and righteous.
What?
I just...
I just want to be normal!
In the end, Kasuga,
you're just the same as the rest of them.
Laughing at meaningless shit
laughing like idiots,
clumping together like sheep in a herd.
You're all scum that'd be better off dead!
A mindless big pile of shit!
Every damn one of you
has nothing in your head but sex!
All of you just want fucking sex!
How boring.
It's boring.
Boring! Boring! Boring!
Boring! Boring!
Our contract is over.
Don't ever speak to me again.
Wait! Nakamura!
I...
took Nanako Saeki's gym clothes
and stole them.
I sniffed them,
and wore them,
and went on a date,
and confessed my love wearing them.
:cue
Despite being her boyfriend,
I kept hiding it from her.
That piece of shit,
the worst pervert
in this town,
is me,
Takao Kasuga.
There, I wrote it.
That's it?
Get it all out!
Spew out everything inside you, Kasuga!
Change this classroom
into a sea of shit bugs for me!
Fuck it!
I'm a despicable human being.
I'm a pervert.
I'm a shit bug!
More!
It's still so boring!
Show me more!
Shit!
Stupid shit bug! I am a pervert!
You little shit bug!
Huh?
More!
More, more, more!
I AM A SHIT BUG
Boring, boring, boring, boring!
Watch this, Baudelaire!
Kasuga...
It was just as I thought.
You're a true pervert.
TO BE CONTINUED
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
In despair over himself,
Kasuga runs off with Nakamura.
But Saeki does not intend
to let go of Kasuga.
Next, on episode four.
Three souls, soaked by the rain,
rub against each other.
Translated by Yuka Kristi